Fear is rising.
Beneath Still Waters is a horror film directed by Brian Yuzna.
Studying under a disciple of Aleister Crowley, the leader of an upper class group invokes a supernatural force that slowly
devours the village of Marienbad and its inhabitants, threatening to spread beyond its geographical limits.
The mayor from the town nearby commissions the building of a dam which would flood the valley and therefore submerge the village
forever sealing the evil force under water after leader and his followers were incapacitated to be kept from escaping.
However, fate ensured the leader's freedom as he remained in
the depths when the waters covered Marienbad.
Now 40 years later an array of disappearances and deaths in mysterious circumstances are
threatening the town next to the reservoir that now covers Marienbad.
Dan Quarry, played by Michael McKell.
Teresa Borgia, played by Raquel Meroño.
Clara Borgia, played by Charlotte Salt.
Mordecai Salas, played by Patrick Gordon.
Susana, played by Pilar Soto.
Luis, played by Manuel Manquiña.
Beneath Still Waters (Spanish: Bajo aguas tranquilas) is a
2005 horror film directed by Brian Yuzna.
It stars Michael McKell, Raquel Meroño and Charlotte Salt.
It is based on a novel by Matthew Costello.
The tone is dark.